Lights go out and I can’t be saved
Tides that I tried to swim against
Have brought me down upon my knees
Oh I beg, I beg and plead, singing
Come out of things unsaid
Shoot an apple off my head and a
Trouble that can’t be named
A tiger’s waiting to be tamed, singing
You are
You are, you are
Confusion never stops
Closing walls and ticking clocksgonna
Come back and take you home
I could not stop that you now know, singing
Come out upon my seas
Cursed missed opportunities
Am I a part of the cure?
Or am I part of thedisease? Singing
You are, you are, you are
You are, you are
And nothing else compares
Oh nothing else compares, And nothing else compares
Home, home, where I wanted to go
Home, home where I wanted to go